### Contact

276-696-1163 (Mobile) jdm7dv@virginia.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/jdm7dv (LinkedIn)

www.jonathanmoore.net (Personal)

## Top Skills

**WPF** 

C++

Visual Studio

### Honors-Awards

**Honor Society** Webby Award Royal Society Of The Arts **Fellowship** 

# Jonathan Moore

UX, Sound Design, Audio and Software Engineer Abingdon, Virginia

## Summary

I began my professional career right out of high school in technical support and development as a Macromedia User Group then later worked for Adobe and FreeBSD volunteer and contributor. At the same time pursuing my associates and bachelors in computer science. I graduated summa cum laude from Tenn. Tech and a UVa alumni. I was also a web developer for the UVa-Wise Magazine. And member of the ACM. My complete discography is available on Bandcamp. I'm a BMI writer and publisher. I have been streamed worldwide with Tunecore And developed some small VST's and Rack Extensions for Propellerhead and Steinberg which never shipped. I recently became a Microsoft Visual Studio industry partner and created a Microsoft Research and Innovation group on Gitlab. Also trying to find some time for sound design and amateur asteroid hunting with MPC. I'm in the Virginia and National Associations for the Gifted since 2011 and Mensa groups here on LinkedIn And IEEE Computer Society also a member of the Mensa High IQ society on LinkedIn I also have been a Microsoft MVP. I am wanting to pursue gifted studies at the University of Connecticut maybe. I scored a 140 on the Mensa mobile app. . Sixtrack is the infrastructure that helps upgrade the LHC.

# Experience

Ableton

Organizer

October 2017 - Present

User Group Organizer, and Github User Group Engineer.

https://www.ableton.com/en/community/user-groups/tri-cities-ableton-usergroup/

https://github.com/AbletonTriCitiesUserGroup

http://www.abletontricitiesusergroup.com/

Google Research Partner November 2017 - Present Abingdon, Va

Artificial Intelligence with Google's Deep Mind, Tensorflow, and Magenta

(independent) Electronic Musician March 2005 - Present Abingdon, Va

https://jdm7dv.bandcamp.com/

Human Brain Project Research Collaborator December 2017 - Present

Microsoft Senior Software Development Engineer October 2004 - Present

Currently at individual status. And a linked Microsoft Research Github. And owner of the Microsoft Research Group on Gitlab. Former Office 365 Partner. Current Visual Studio Industry Partner

#### Macromedia

Technical Support
December 2000 - October 2006 (5 years 11 months)

Originally a Macromedia User Group focusing on Flash special FX and UI prototyping. Also Director Shockwave. Then Adobe employee.

AVID Audio Visual Installation & Design Audio Engineer April 2002 - December 2004 (2 years 9 months) Originally Digidesign, Digidesign Partner

## Education

Stanford University

Stanford Online, Quantum Mechanics for Scientists and Engineers  $\cdot$  (2016)

edX

Computer Music, Nanotechnology, Artifical Intelligence, Computation Structures · (2015 - 2020)

University of Virginia

Bachelor of Science, Computer Software Engineering · (2008 - 2013)

Tennessee College of Applied Technology - Nashville Associate's Degree, Computer Science · (1999 - 2001)